Guide to the Time Inc. Time Editorial Records 1938-2009 MS 3009-RG 7
New-York Historical Society
- Series II.B. Executive Editor Edward Jamieson Files, 1957-1986; 37 Linear feet in 37 record cartons
  - Subseries II.B.2. Subject Files, 1957-1985; 17.75 Linear feet in 19 record cartons
    - 1975: Essay: Master Lists (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 43)
    - 1975: Europe Edition: Move to New York (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 44)
    - 1975: European Budget [empty] (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 45)
    - 1975: European Supplement [empty] (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 46)
    - 1975: Expense Reports (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 47-48)
    - 1975: Fortune Economic Forecasts (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 49)
    - 1975: General Increase (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 50)
    - 1975: Grunwald, Henry: Job Description Sheet (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 51)
      Includes Grunwald's recounting of his day-to-day activities.
    - 1975: Holidays and Closings (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 52)
    - 1975: Kissinger, Henry: Talk (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 53)
    - 1975: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 1-2)
    - 1975: Merrill, David: Flopped Art Page (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 3)
    - 1975: Newsstand Circulation (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 4)
    - 1975: Newsstand Sales Figures (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 5)
    - 1975: Newstour (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 6)
    - 1975: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Cover and Color Comparisons, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 7-9)
    - 1975: Picture Procurement Cost Comparisons, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 10)
    - 1975: Seminar on Time's Future, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 11)
    - 1975: State Department Foreign Journalist Exchange (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 12)
    - 1975: Subscriber Delivery Report (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 13)
    - 1975: Summer Reading (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 14)
    - 1975: Syndication of Time Material in Canada (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 15)
    - 1975: Time Canada (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 16)
    - 1976: Affirmative Action Memorandum from James Shepley (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 17)
    - 1976: Annapolis (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 18)
    - 1976: Back-of-the-Book Cluster Sections (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 19)
    - 1976: Bangladesh Lunch (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 20)
    - 1976: Bicentennial (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 21-22)
    - 1976: Boat Party (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 23)
    - 1976: Books Borrowed (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 24-25)
    - 1976: Budget (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 26)
    - 1976: Business Section (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 27-29)
    - 1976: Cafiero, Eugene: Meeting (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 30)
    - 1976: Carter, Jimmy (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 31)
    - 1976: Close Report (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 32)
    - 1976: Color Schedule (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 33)
    - 1976: Commas (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 34)
    - 1976: Communications Department (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 35)
    - 1976: Copy Processing Weekly Report (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 36)
    - 1976: Cover (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 37)
    - 1976: Cover: Credit (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 38)
    - 1976: Cover: Schedule (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 39-40)
    - 1976: Cover: Second Billing Test (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 41)
    - 1976: Cover: Subject Weekly Report (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 42)
    - 1976: Editorial Awards (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 43)
    - 1976: Editorial Change Account (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 44-45)
    - 1976: Editorial Management Training (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 46)
    - 1976: Editors and Writers From Bureaus (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 47)
    - 1976: Election Issue (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 48-49)
    - 1976: Elson, John (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 50)
    - 1976: Essay (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 51)
    - 1976: Essay: Line Count (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 52)
    - 1976: Essay: Religion and War (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 53)
    - 1976: European Edition: Business, Economy, Trade Content (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 54)
    - 1976: Expense Accounts (Offsite-box 2450, Folder 55)
    - 1976: Fashion Color Issue (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 1)
    - 1976: Ford Foundation Education (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 2)
    - 1976: Holidays (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 3-5)
    - 1976: Late Hours (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 6)
    - 1976: Leadership Conference (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 7)
    - 1976: Legal Department Beeper System (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 8)
    - 1976: Loeb Rhodes Report (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 9-10)
    - 1976: Man of the Year (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 11)
    - 1976: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 12-14)
    - 1976: Medical Articles (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 15)
    - 1976: Message to America (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 16)
    - 1976: Mobility (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 17)
    - 1976: Newsstand Sales Figures (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 18)
    - 1976: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 19)
    - 1976: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Cover and Color Comparison (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 20-23)
    - 1976: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Share of Market (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 24)
    - 1976: Newsweek: Speech (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 25)
    - 1976: Olympics Plan (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 26)
    - 1976: Outside Writing, 1972-1976 (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 27)
    - 1976: Page Count (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 28)
    - 1976: Playboy Lunch (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 29)
    - 1976: Political Conventions: Democratic (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 30)
    - 1976: Political Conventions: Republican (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 31-32)
    - 1976: Promotion to Executive Editor (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 33)
    - 1976: Public Agenda Foundation: Inflation and Unemployment (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 34)
    - 1976: Random House: Hughes Contract (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 35)
    - 1976: Random House: Hughes Contract [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1976: Reader Research (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 36)
    - 1976: Research Reorganization Memorandum (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 37)
    - 1976: Researcher Procedures (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 38)
    - 1976: Restaurants with Private Dining Facilties (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 39)
    - 1976: Saturday Duty (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 40)
    - 1976: Secret Service Memorandum (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 41)
    - 1976: Simmons and TGI Report (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 42)
    - 1976: Staff Publicity (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 43)
    - 1976: Strike (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 44-49)
    - 1976: Time International (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 50)
    - 1976: Time Issues Remaining Before Election (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 51)
    - 1976: Visual Graphics Contract (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 52)
    - 1976: Writer Corespondent List (Offsite-box 2451, Folder 53)
    - 1977: Affidavit: "Flimflam Man" (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 1)
    - 1977: Books to Cape Cod (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 2-3)
    - 1977: Budget (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 4-5)
    - 1977: Cave, Ray: Cautionary Note (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 6)
    - 1977: Change Premiums (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 7)
    - 1977: Color Printing and Schedule (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 8-9)
    - 1977: Correspondents Meeting (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 10)
    - 1977: Cover: Schedules (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 11)
    - 1977: Cover: Special Covers Lists (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 12)
    - 1977: Cover: Story: The Family and Protectionism (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 13)
    - 1977: Cover: Suggestions (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 14-15)
    - 1977: The Crucial Comma (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 16)
    - 1977: Distribution Planning (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 17)
    - 1977: Editorial Copy Preparation System Alternate (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 18)
    - 1977: Edit Pages (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 19-20)
    - 1977: Essay Suggestions (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 21)
    - 1977: Evaluations (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 22-23)
    - 1977: Expense Accounts (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 24)
    - 1977: Extraordinary Hours Worked (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 25)
    - 1977: Freelance Work on Leave (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 26)
    - 1977: Gallup Consumer Survey (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 27)
    - 1977: Holidays (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 28)
    - 1977: Issue Review (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 29-30)
    - 1977: Job Posting Policy (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 31)
    - 1977: Louis Harris Study on Energy (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 32)
    - 1977: Man of the Year (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 33)
    - 1977: Map Room (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 34)
    - 1977: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 35-36)
    - 1977: New Copy Processing Facilities (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 37)
    - 1977: New Design (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 38)
    - 1977: News Clippings (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 39)
    - 1977: News Desk: Mini Computer System (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 40-41)
    - 1977: Newsstand Sales Analysis and Sales (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 42-43)
    - 1977: Outside Writing (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 44)
    - 1977: Planning for 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 45)
    - 1977: Questionnaire on Subscriber Attitudes Toward Time (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 46)
      The results are not included.
    - 1977: Saturday Duty Lists (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 47)
    - 1977: Senior Editors Lunch (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 48)
    - 1977: Softball Schedule (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 49)
    - 1977: Staff Development (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 50)
    - 1977: Stock Market Stakes (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 51)
    - 1977: Time "B" Folder (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 52)
    - 1977: Time Outing (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 53)
    - 1977: Time: Readers Interest in News (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 54)
    - 1977: 24th Floor Fire Trap Memorandum (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 55)
    - 1977: Underclass Conference Possibilities (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 56)
    - 1977: Waite, Elizabeth: Courier Trips (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 57)
    - 1977: Weinstein, Allen: Hiss Case (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 58)
    - 1977: Wyeth, James / Robert Lescher Contract [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1977: Youth Edition (Offsite-box 2452, Folder 59)
    - 1978: African Americans at Time Inc. (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 1)
    - 1978: Alexander, Roy: Obituaries (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 2)
    - 1978: Benefit Plans (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 3)
    - 1978: Books Borrowed (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 4-5)
    - 1978: Budget (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 6)
    - 1978: Cave, Ray: Schedule (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 7)
    - 1978: Chagall, Marc: Obituary (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 8)
    - 1978: Contributors Contract (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 9)
    - 1978: Covers (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 10-12)
    - 1978: Covers Inventory (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 13)
    - 1978: Covers: Study of Time Covers (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 14)
    - 1978: Covers: Suggestions (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 15)
    - 1978: Covers: The United States Family (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 16)
    - 1978: Cultural Explosion (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 17)
    - 1978: Defense Round Table (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 18)
    - 1978: Dial A Steak (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 19)
    - 1978: Dow Jones Management Staff (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 20)
    - 1978: Editorial Closings (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 21)
    - 1978: Editorial Payments Made (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 22)
    - 1978: Editorial News Service Exchange Program (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 23)
    - 1978: Essays: Chronological List (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 24)
    - 1978: Essays: Suggestions (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 25)
    - 1978: Evaluations (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 26)
    - 1978: Executive View (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 27)
    - 1978: Expense Accounts (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 28)
    - 1978: Five Year Plan (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 29)
    - 1978: Future Book Excerpts (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 30)
    - 1978: Holidays (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 31)
    - 1978: Internship Program (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 32)
    - 1978: Kissinger, Henry: Contract [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1978: Kissinger, Henry: International Creative Management (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 33)
    - 1978: Maui, Hawaii Possible Story (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 34)
    - 1978: Minorities and Women (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 35)
    - 1978: New Training Category (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 36)
    - 1978: Newspaper Guild Negotiations (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 37)
    - 1978: News Service (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 38)
    - 1978: News Service: Five Year Plan (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 39)
    - 1978: Newsstand Sales Figure (Offsite-box 2453, Folder 40-41)
    - 1978: Newstour (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 1-2)
    - 1978: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Color Comparison (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 3)
    - 1978: Outside Writing (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 4)
    - 1978: Premiums for Issue (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 5)
    - 1978: Rorvik, David (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 6)
    - 1978: Saturday Duty Lists (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 7)
    - 1978: Trip: Ireland (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 8)
    - 1978: 20-20: Robert Hughes Show (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 9)
    - 1978: Votes on July 4th Holiday (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 10)
    - 1978: Weinstein, Allen: Hiss/Chambers: Julian Bach Literary Agency (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 11)
    - 1979: American Scene (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 12)
    - 1979: Budget (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 13-14)
    - 1979: Budget: International (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 15)
    - 1979: Cover Lists (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 16)
    - 1979: Dinner Lists (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 17)
    - 1979: General Evaluations (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 18)
    - 1979: Holidays: Guild (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 19)
    - 1979: Holidays: Memoranda (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 20)
    - 1979: New Chinese Spellings (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 21)
    - 1979: Pension Plan? (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 22)
    - 1979: Summer Olympics (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 23)
    - 1979: Worldwide Operation Plans (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 24)
    - 1980: Cover Lists (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 25)
    - 1980: Time 1981-1985 Plan (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 26)
    - 1981: Budget (Offsite-box 2454, Folder 27-29)
    - 1981: Duke University (Offsite-box 2455, Folder 1)
    - 1981: Jamieson, Edward: Photograph (Offsite-box 2455, Folder 2)
    - 1981: Man of the Year (Offsite-box 2455, Folder 3-4)
    - 1981: Masthead (Offsite-box 2455, Folder 5-6)
    - 1981: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Newsstand Sales (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 7-8)
    - 1981: Sweeney, Katherine (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 9)
    - 1981: Weekend Lawyers (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 10)
    - 1982: Newsstand Sales Figures (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 11)
    - 1982: Story Copy (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 12)
    - 1983: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 13-17)
    - 1983: Newsstand Sales Figures (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 18-19)
    - 1983: Time-Life Alumni Society (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 20)
    - 1984: Alheimer's Disease (Offsite-box 2455, Folder 21)
    - 1984: Cheese (Offsite-box 2455, Folder 22)
    - 1984: Cover: Britain (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 1)
    - 1984: Employee Option Survey (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 2-3)
    - 1984: Gardner, Martin: Reports (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 4)
    - 1984: Hill, Ernie: Pending (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 5)
    - 1984: Hoffmann, Heinrich: Photographs (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 6)
    - 1984: International Monetary Fund Notes (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 7)
    - 1984: Muller, Henry: Memoranda (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 8)
    - 1984: New Section: New and Noteworthy (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 9)
    - 1984: Overtime (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 10)
    - 1984: Reagan in China (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 11)
    - 1984: Senior Editors: Possibilities [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1984: Trip Itinerary (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 12-13)
    - 1985: Economy and Business Forum (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 14)
    - Undated: Office Layouts (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 8)
  - Subseries II.B.3. Printed Matter, 1966-1984; 1.25 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    Printed Matter includes contact lists, employee benefits booklets and handbooks, department structure lists, and other directories and guides regularly distributed to Jamieson's office for reference purposes.
    - Christmas List, 1974 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 15)
    - Dialcab Rate Booklet, circa 1977 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 16)
    - Directory of Foreign Bureaus, 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 19-20)
    - Directory of News Service Bureaus and Stringers, 1970-1974 (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 6)
    - Employee Benefits, 1967, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 17)
    - Employee Handbook, 1966, 1970 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 18)
    - F.Y.I Inserts, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 9)
    - Holiday Address List, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 21)
    - Home Address List, 1972-1980 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 22-24)
    - IBM Typewriter Style Guide, 1978 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 25)
    - Newspaper Guild Contract, 1971 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 26)
    - Rockefeller Center Shops and Services Directory, 1968 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 10)
    - Temporary Talents / Laskay Business Services, undated (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 13)
    - Time Editorial Staff List, 1977 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 27)
    - Time Inc. Department Head Directory, 1971-1982 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 28-33)
    - Time Inc. Telephone Directory, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 11-12)
    - Time Inc. Telephone Directory, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 2456, Folder 34-36)
    - Time Inc. Telephone Directory, 1974-1983 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 1-5)
    - Time Inc. Telephone Directory: "541" (Chicago), 1972 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 6)
    - Time Life Books Employee Price List, 1973-1976, 1984 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 7)
    - Time Rate Card, 1968 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 14)
  - Subseries II.B.4.a. Personnel: Administrative Files, 1966-1982; 2.25 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    Personnel Administration Files include records created while hiring and managing Time Editorial employees that are not personnel records. Records include correspondence and memoranda on policies, different categories of staff, the internship program, and lists for vacation tracking.
    - General, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 15-17)
    - General [RESTRICTED], 1967-1971 (Offsite-box R39)
    - Administrative Assistant, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Assistant for Managing Editor, 1976 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 8)
    - Consultants, 1976-1982 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 9-11)
    - Contracts: Copies [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R39)
    - Contracts: Memorandum, 1978 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 12)
    - Contract Writers, 1980 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 13)
    - Contributor Agreements [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R39)
    - Contributor Contracts and Reports, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 14-16)
    - Correspondents in New York, 1979 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 17)
    - Departed Time, 1977 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 18)
    - Evaluations, 1981 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 19)
    - Evaluations [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - Head Count, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 20-24)
    - Hires from Life, 1972 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 25)
    - Interns: General, 1977 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 26)
    - Interns: General [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - Interns: Summer Intern Program, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 27-29)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1981 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 30a)
    - Minimum Pay Rates, 1972 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 19)
    - New Writers, 1977-1981 (Offsite-box 2458, Folder 30b-30d)
    - Newspaper Guild, 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 20-22)
    - Payments and Policies, 1970 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 23)
    - Raises [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Offsite-box R39)
    - Retirees, 1977 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 31)
    - Retirement Dates, 1977 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 32)
    - Special Consultants, 1975 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 33-34)
    - Staff List Changes, 1972 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 24)
    - Stock Options, 1972 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 25)
    - Stringer Payment: American Scene, 1978 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 35)
    - Time Editorial Addresses, 1970 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 26)
    - Time-Life News Bureau Lists, 1970 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 27)
    - Time Promotion System, 1970 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 28)
    - Vacations, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 29-32)
    - Vacations, 1973-1982 (Offsite-box 2457, Folder 36-50)
    - Vacation: Addresses, 1972 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 33)
    - Vacation: List, 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 2458, Folder 1-3)
    - Vacation: Reports, 1971-1976 (Offsite-box 2458, Folder 4-8)
    - Vacation: Requests, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 34-35)
    - Vacation: Requests, 1973-1983 (Offsite-box 2458, Folder 9-17)
    - Vacation: Schedules, 1966-1979 (Offsite-box 2458, Folder 18-24)
    - Vacation: Senior Editor Replacements, 1974 (Offsite-box 2458, Folder 25)
    - Vacation: Substitutes, 1975 (Offsite-box 2458, Folder 26)
    - Vacation: Time Europe, 1974 (Offsite-box 2458, Folder 27)
    - Vacation: Time Not Taken, 1977 (Offsite-box 2458, Folder 28)
    - Vacation: Waite, Elizabeth, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 36-37)
  - Subseries II.B.4.b. Personnel: Employees Files [RESTRICTED], circa 1969-circa 1986; 5.25 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
    Employees Files include correspondence, applications, reference letters, leave requests, termination records, and other employment records.
    Organized in alphabetical order by last name with general files and index cards at the front.
    - General, 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 2459)
    - Index Cards, 1970s (Offsite-box 2460, Folder 1-3)
    - Adams - Elmer-DeWitt, circa 1969-circa 1986 (Offsite-box 2460, Folder 4-62)
    - Anson - Zimmerman, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box R39)
    - Ehrlichman - Morris, circa 1969-circa 1986 (Offsite-box 2461)
    - Morrison - Seamon, circa 1969-circa 1986 (Offsite-box 2462)
    - Serrill - Zoglin, circa 1969-circa 1986 (Offsite-box 2463)
- Series II.C. Executive Editor Joelle Attinger Files on the 1999 Newstour, 2 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
  According to her bio in the China 1999 Participants packet, Joëlle Attinger joined Time in 1973 as a correspondent before serving as bureau chief and deputy chief of correspondents for the news service. In 1993 she was named Assistant Managing Editor and Chief of Correspondents. In 1997 she became the first woman to hold the highest editorial position at Time, the role of Executive Editor..
  It looks like Attinger was involved with the planning of the 1999 newstour to China. According to a packet on the history of Time Newstours in Editor-in-Chief Henry Grunwald's files, "the purpose of the Newstour is to give an opportunity to a small group of American leaders to visit areas of the world currently in the news..." The majority of prior newstours were organized by Time Promotion and Public Affairs staff with one in 1995 organized by Corporate Public Affairs.
  Joëlle Attinger's files on the 1999 newstour to China include information on participants, a collection of business cards from participants and hosts, global intelligence updates, itineraries, mailings sent to participants, flights, hotels, and visas. Additional files on CHINA 1999 are in Jean C. Gussenhoven's files in Time Publishing and Business Records. Unreformatted audiovisual and digital material in the collection is not accessible.
  - CHINA 1999 (Offsite-box 3292)
  - CHINA 1999 (Offsite-box 3293, Folder 1-24)
    Includes audiovisual material:
    1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "Legacy of Tiananmen China's Cultural Revolution."
  - CHINA 1999: Participants Visas (binder cover) (Offsite-box 2830, Folder 1)
  - CHINA 1999 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39, Folder 61-64)
    Includes digital material in the folder "Computer Files":
    8 computer discs (floppy disk): 3 1/2 in.
- Series III.A. Art Department: Cover Researcher Rosemary Frank Files, 1948-2009 (bulk 1963-1988); 20 Linear feet in 20 record cartons